conductor.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Conductor

Conductor, Inc. (hereafter referred to as "Conductor") wants you to fully understand our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information through our websites located at URLs: [www.conductor.com](http://www.conductor.com/ "www.conductor.com"), console.conductor.com, or any other Conductor owned site collectively know as (the "websites"). "Personal Information" means information that would allow a party to contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, or email address.

Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. Conductor reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and without any notice by posting a revised Privacy Policy on our website. Any such revision will become effective immediately upon posting.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We do not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. Although we may disclose aggregated information about the use of our websites, that information does not contain Personal Information. Generally, we do not disclose Personal Information to third parties. However, we may share Personal Information with our contractors and service providers in order to maintain, enhance, or add to the functionality of the websites. If Conductor becomes part of another organization, that organization will possess the Personal Information collected by Conductor and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We cannot ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

**Communications**

If you have registered to receive email communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. To Opt-out send an email to [optout@conductor.com](mailto:optout@conductor.com). Please reference "Opt-Out" in your subject line and state in the body of the email that you wish to have your name removed from the distribution lists.

**Information We Collect and How We Use That Information**

Our registration forms require users to provide contact information, including name, physical address, company information, website information, website statistics, email address, and similar information ("Personal Information"). We store sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card information. We track data to monitor utilization and ensure good customer experience.

We will use your Personal Information only to perform services you have requested, including the completion of financial transactions. In order to perform and complete these services and transactions, we may provide personally identifiable information to third parties. We will never sell or share your personal information with any third parties other than for these services which you request or to comply with legal requirements.

Conductor uses a single crawler that respects industry standards when gathering web data. We use your domain's robots.txt file to tell us which files we can search and which files to leave alone. You can also control how often we search your site. To learn more about Conductor's Caliperbot  click here.

**Internet Protocol Address**

We collect Internet Protocol ("IP") address from all visitors to the website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the website, and deliver customized, personalized content.

**Use of "Cookies"**

Cookies are pieces of data created when you visit a site. The cookies sets by the Conductor servers are unique, anonymous numbers. They are stored by your browser on your hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. If you choose not to accept the cookie, this will affect your access to the majority of facilities available on our website.

Although your browser may be set up to allow the creation of cookies, you can specify that you be prompted before a site puts a cookie on your hard disk, so that you can decide whether to allow or disallow the cookie. Alternatively, you can set your computer not to accept any cookie. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to some features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location.

All credit card information is encrypted before it is transmitted across the network or stored in our systems. We use strong encryption as mandated by the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standards developed by Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover Card. Conductor complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.

**Other websites**

Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website over which Conductor has no control and will bear no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such websites as their policies may be different than ours.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose your Personal Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Conductor.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or your dealings with this website, or would like to make corrections to Personal Information which you submitted, you can e-mail us at info at our domain name.com
